const e=JSON.parse('[{"question":"0 - 0 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"1","correct":false},{"answer":"0","correct":true},{"answer":"3","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"1 - 0 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":true},{"answer":"0","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"1 - 1 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"3","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"0","correct":true}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"2 - 0 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"1","correct":false},{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":true}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"2 - 1 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":true},{"answer":"0","correct":false},{"answer":"3","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"2 - 2 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"0","correct":true},{"answer":"3","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"3 - 0 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"7","correct":false},{"answer":"3","correct":true},{"answer":"6","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"3 - 1 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":true},{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"6","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"3 - 2 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":true},{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"0","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"3 - 3 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"1","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"3","correct":false},{"answer":"0","correct":true}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"4 - 0 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"0","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":true},{"answer":"5","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"4 - 1 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"6","correct":false},{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"3","correct":true}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"4 - 2 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"2","correct":true},{"answer":"3","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"4 - 3 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"1","correct":true},{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"0","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"4 - 4 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"0","correct":true}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"5 - 0 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"5","correct":true},{"answer":"1","correct":false},{"answer":"7","correct":false},{"answer":"6","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"5 - 1 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":true},{"answer":"0","correct":false},{"answer":"6","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"5 - 2 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"3","correct":true},{"answer":"6","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"5 - 3 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"0","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":true},{"answer":"1","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"5 - 4 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"0","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":true},{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"5 - 5 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"0","correct":true},{"answer":"3","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"6 - 0 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"6","correct":true},{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"8","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"6 - 1 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"6","correct":false},{"answer":"8","correct":false},{"answer":"5","correct":true},{"answer":"1","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"6 - 2 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"4","correct":true},{"answer":"1","correct":false},{"answer":"0","correct":false},{"answer":"7","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"6 - 3 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"6","correct":false},{"answer":"3","correct":true},{"answer":"7","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"6 - 4 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":true},{"answer":"0","correct":false},{"answer":"6","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"6 - 5 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"0","correct":false},{"answer":"3","correct":false},{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":true}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"6 - 6 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"3","correct":false},{"answer":"0","correct":true},{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"7 - 0 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"10","correct":false},{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"7","correct":true}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"7 - 1 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"6","correct":true},{"answer":"8","correct":false},{"answer":"7","correct":false},{"answer":"3","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"7 - 2 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"5","correct":true},{"answer":"1","correct":false},{"answer":"7","correct":false},{"answer":"8","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"7 - 3 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"8","correct":false},{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":true}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"7 - 4 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"7","correct":false},{"answer":"3","correct":true},{"answer":"4","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"7 - 5 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":true},{"answer":"0","correct":false},{"answer":"6","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"7 - 6 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":true},{"answer":"0","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"7 - 7 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"0","correct":true},{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"8 - 0 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"10","correct":false},{"answer":"12","correct":false},{"answer":"8","correct":true},{"answer":"9","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"8 - 1 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"7","correct":true},{"answer":"6","correct":false},{"answer":"10","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"8 - 2 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"6","correct":true},{"answer":"9","correct":false},{"answer":"8","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"8 - 3 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"5","correct":true},{"answer":"9","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":false},{"answer":"8","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"8 - 4 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"0","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":true},{"answer":"3","correct":false},{"answer":"6","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"8 - 5 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"3","correct":true},{"answer":"0","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"8 - 6 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"1","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":true},{"answer":"3","correct":false},{"answer":"6","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"8 - 7 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":true},{"answer":"0","correct":false},{"answer":"3","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"8 - 8 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"1","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"0","correct":true},{"answer":"2","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"9 - 0 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"10","correct":false},{"answer":"9","correct":true},{"answer":"12","correct":false},{"answer":"11","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"9 - 1 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"10","correct":false},{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"8","correct":true},{"answer":"11","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"9 - 2 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"7","correct":true},{"answer":"3","correct":false},{"answer":"9","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"9 - 3 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"7","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"6","correct":true},{"answer":"4","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"9 - 4 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"5","correct":true},{"answer":"6","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"7","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"9 - 5 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"4","correct":true},{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"7","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"9 - 6 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"0","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"6","correct":false},{"answer":"3","correct":true}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"9 - 7 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"2","correct":true},{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"6","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"9 - 8 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"1","correct":true},{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"5","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"9 - 9 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"0","correct":true},{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"3","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"10 - 0 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"7","correct":false},{"answer":"12","correct":false},{"answer":"13","correct":false},{"answer":"10","correct":true}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"10 - 1 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"9","correct":true},{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"12","correct":false},{"answer":"11","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"10 - 2 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"7","correct":false},{"answer":"11","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"8","correct":true}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"10 - 3 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"8","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"3","correct":false},{"answer":"7","correct":true}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"10 - 4 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"7","correct":false},{"answer":"6","correct":true},{"answer":"9","correct":false},{"answer":"5","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"10 - 5 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"6","correct":false},{"answer":"5","correct":true},{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"10 - 6 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"6","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":true},{"answer":"7","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"10 - 7 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"7","correct":false},{"answer":"0","correct":false},{"answer":"3","correct":true}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"10 - 8 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"6","correct":false},{"answer":"2","correct":true},{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"5","correct":false}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"10 - 9 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"5","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"3","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":true}],"selectedAnswer":null},{"question":"10 - 10 = ?","answers":[{"answer":"2","correct":false},{"answer":"1","correct":false},{"answer":"4","correct":false},{"answer":"0","correct":true}],"selectedAnswer":null}]');export{e as default};
//# sourceMappingURL=soustraction-BvoZAQ7j.js.map
